All right, good morning everybody. Uh,
thank you guys all for coming out. I
know it was a a quick turn after last
night. Um, none quicker than the uh,
gentleman off to my left here and the
the crew sitting sitting down here in
front. So, uh, before we get going and
and turn it over to Jeremiah, who that's
the one you're all here to talk to, um,
just want to welcome a few people. Um,
you know, Jeremiah has got his family in
town here, his mom and dad, uh, Jason
and Latana, uh, sister Jayla and
girlfriend Unique. Um, you know, we got
some some flowers for them. I just
appreciate you guys and and, uh, what
you've done to to get you Jeremiah here.
[laughter] Hands off, Dad.
Uh but again guys, we're we spoke last
night a little bit. Um excited for you
guys to get a chance to talk to Jeremiah
um for for as good of a football player
is on the field. Um and even better
person off the field and you guys are
going to find that out real quickly
here. So, uh you know, you've heard
enough from me already. I want to get
Jeremiah up here and give you a chance
to talk to him. So, newest member of the
Arizona Cardinals, Jeremiah Love.
[applause]
Glad to be here, guys. Um, glad to see
all you guys' faces. I'm looking forward
to building great relationships with you
all. Um, just want to thank you to, uh,
Mr. Bidwell and, um, you know, everybody
that's believed in me to, you know, let
me allow me to stand here right now. Um,
you know, thank you to God as well.
Thank you to my family and um thank you
to these special gentlemen over here for
just giving me a chance. But um I'm
ready to work. I'm here to work and uh
thank you for believing in me and you
want to do some great things.
>> We will open up to questions. We have
Mike with the microphone over here and
in the middle. So just get their
attention and if you don't mind just
saying your name and your ailation.
Richard signs.
>> Jeremiah Richard signs Fox 10. Welcome
to the Valley. Uh you know this is
obviously a big day for you. a dream
come true, I would imagine. Just tell us
uh what it's like for not just you, but
for your support system, your your
family that's here, and that obviously
means so much to you.
>> Um it's everything to us, you know. Um
we've worked so hard to get here. You
know, we sacrificed a lot to get here.
My mom and dad, you know, I've
sacrificed a lot of their time. Um my
mom and dad were police officers growing
up, so you can only imagine how the
household was. You know, my sister went
to school to be a nurse, so she's always
grinding. And then shoot, everybody
just, you know, putting in to get me
here. So, it's very it's a very special
moment for us all and um we're very
grateful for this opportunity and um
like I said, I'm here to work and I'm
ready to work and uh I'm going to make
sure that I take advantage of every
single opportunity that I get and uh
we're going to do some great things. But
we're all grateful for uh this moment
and we're blessed to be here and the
only reason we're here is because of
God.
>> Hey Jeremiah, Mark Mcclo, Arizona's
family 3TV CBS 5. Welcome to the Valley.
Hey, wanted to ask you specifically
about uh ball security because you look
at the numbers and you're able to hold
on to the football. So, uh what's your
philosophy when it comes to that? A lot
of people talk about it, but how are you
able to to execute holding on to it? And
>> so, ball security is everything. You
know, the ball is the game. You know,
without the ball, you can't win games.
So, um when I first got to college, my
running back's coach, Da McCulla, um
shoot right from the bat, you know, told
me the importance of ball security. And
I kid you not, in literally the stretch
lines, my very first stretch line, he
gave me like this beeper ball and I had
to hold it throughout the whole stretch
throughout the little whole little
warm-up run and it had to be beeping the
whole time. If it wasn't beeping, you
got to redo everything. So, um, Coach
McCulla is the first person, you know,
when I came to college that emphasized
the importance of ball security and it
just stuck with me the whole way. And
I'm sure you can see some pictures of me
running the end zone with, you know,
having the ball capped and, you know,
that's what it's all about, protecting
the football, protecting the
quarterback. And you know, that's what
I'm going to do as a running back,
protect that ball and allow and and
allow us to have uh success.
>> Hey Jeremiah, I'm Josh Weinfest, ESPN.
Last night you told us that you're on
the hunt for something greater. Can you
kind of expand on that? What is that
something greater and what does that
look like in the short term and the long
term?
>> So obviously me being drafted um number
three to come to the Cardinals is a
blessing. You know, it's a dream come
true. But what I what I meant when I
said I'm on the hunt for something
greater is wanted to convey that I'm not
complacent. You know, I'm not satisfied
from just getting here. You know, I want
to be a Hall of Famer by the end of my
time playing. You know, I want to be one
of the greatest running backs to come
through the game. So, I'm always on the
hunt for something greater. And then
even after football, I'm on the hunt for
something greater. You know, go back to
school and get my degree. Um, I wanted
to become a doctor before I played
football. So, um, throughout life, I'm
always going to be on the hunt for
something greater. Um, and that's just
me, you know, that's how I was raised.
My mom and dad told me to never be
complacent, never be satisfied. You
know, Coach Freeman always says, you
know, choose hard and consistently find
ways to get better.
>> Hey Jeremiah, Tyler Drake with Arizona
Sports. Welcome to the Valley. Uh your
Notre Dame running mate, first round
pick as well going to Seattle. Uh what's
the trash uh talk going to be like that?
And what's it just mean to see uh your
running mate go in the first round of
Sue?
>> It means everything. Literally JD was
the first person that I texted, you
know, once I got drafted and once I saw
he got drafted and I got on my phone. JD
was the first person that came to mind.
You know, I've watched JD work for, you
know, three years. You know, we've been
together, you know, been we've been
partnered up in that running back room
for three years. So, I mean, it was
everything to see him get drafted. You
know, I seen him, you know, put in the
work. You know, I seen him, you know,
grind through the injuries and, um, for
him to be able to get drafted and and go
to a great team at that, you know, it
was just a great moment. you know, I
love seeing my guys have success. You
know, that's going to be no different
here. You know, I'm going to build great
relationships with the players, with the
coaches, you know, with the ownership
and, you know, I want this organization
to have success and I'm going to
contribute to that. So, when I saw JD,
you know, get drafted, it was just it
was it was a very, very heartwarming
moment and um I made sure I had to
congratulate him on that.
>> [snorts]
>> Jeremiah Teraki, Arizona Republic. You
talked yesterday about your favorite
runs are the short yardage runs, but
obviously your ability in the open field
is is quite special as well. The ability
to turn 10 into 80. Where does that come
from for you, that that ability in the
open field and at the second level?
>> I would say it all starts from uh me um
playing in high school. my uh head coach
at the time uh his name is Scott Pingle
um made sure that you know I practiced a
certain way you know and that practice
translated to the games and he always
told me he loved my short yardage runs
rather than uh my long run. So um in
practice there was a huge emphasis on
finishing and making sure you're being
gritty and tough. Um and um the saying
at at CBC was uh brick by brick. you
know, you got to to build a to build a
house or to build a a place of staying,
you know, you got to start with a
foundation. You got to build it up brick
by brick. You got to be tough. So, um
that's where the foundation was laid at
CBC uh with Scott Pingle being my head
coach and uh just telling me to make
sure I'm practicing hard, make sure I'm
being greedy and being a tough player.
And then that translated over to
college. You know, I had great coaches
like Coach McCulla. I had a great, you
know, offensive coordinator, Mike Denim
Brock, and then I had a great head coach
that consistently told me to, you know,
be gritty, be tough, and, uh, be
consistent. So, um, that's where I get
it from.
>> Jeremiah Darren Urban from
acardinal.com. I'm curious, everybody
who talks about you talks about what a
great kid you are and how how well you
handle yourself. Um, it also is very
clear that you're a very confident
person. I'm curious. You have all these
people saying you're you were the best
player in the draft. you have all this
talent. How do you walk that line
between trying to stay humble, but also
having that confidence that comes with
what you bring to the table?
>> You know, it all just comes down to just
being myself. You know, a lot of people
say I'm confident. You know, a lot of
people say I'm humble, but at the end of
the day, I'm just being who I am. You
know, and uh however that's portrayed,
that's portrayed. Um but, you know, at
the end of the day, I'm just here to
work, man. I'm I'm I'm blessed to be
here. I'm here to work. And uh that's
how I've gotten here, and that's what
I'm going to continue to do. you know,
find ways to get better on the field and
off the field and just be authentically
me. So, um, thanks for saying I'm
humble. Thanks for saying I'm confident,
but, um, I'm just being myself, man, and
and that's what I'm going to continue to
be.
>> Hi, Jeremiah. Robbie Baker with Fox 10.
Welcome here to Arizona. I'm just
curious what kind of running backs you
enjoyed watching coming up and what
running backs maybe you molded your game
after over the years.
>> Yeah. So, um, I didn't mold my game
after anybody growing up. You know, I
didn't watch football much. You know, my
dad put on some Barry Sander highlights
for me. You know, I like Barry Sanders.
I I think of him as the best running
back of all time. Um, but players that
I've watched, you know, recently, Jir
Gibbs, Seaquan, uh, Derek Henry,
Christian McAffrey, um, Alvin Chimera,
you know, those are all great backs. You
know, I love their playing style. You
know, Jir Gibbs is very quick. You know,
he's very fast. You know, fast burst.
And, um, you know, Chris McAffrey is
recovery. It's great. You know, I got to
talk with him not too long ago. got to
pick his brains because uh my strength
coach at Notre Dame, Lauren Landal, uh
was known Christian his whole life. So,
he connected me and him. Got to talk to
him for a little bit and uh just he
just, you know, advised me on what to do
and how to be a pro coming into this
league. Um and then Derek Henry, big
guy, strong guy, teaches you how to run
tough. And then Alvin Kimera, just the
whole he got the whole toolbox. He can
receive, he can block, he can run. So, I
like to watch him for that. And then I
think the other guy say what I say.
Barry Sanders, it's the best running
back of all time. [laughter]
Yeah.
>> Hey, Jeremiah. Uh, last night Michael
Flores said that you don't have any
weaknesses in your game as pass as a
receiver, as a rusher, and and pass
protection. What is about pass
protection that I guess you enjoy, you
embrace, and how do you balance working
on that with kind of the other parts of
your game?
>> So, so pass protection is the most
important part of my game. you know,
that's probably the the most that's the
only thing I really train on when I'm
when I'm at practice. You know, footwork
is is natural. We we do tuneups, but
pass protection is what we really, you
know, focus on because you got to be
able to protect the ball. You got to be
able to protect the quarterback so that
he can have time to make plays. Um, and
I mean, I like pass protection. I get to
hit people. You know, people always
hitting me. So, whenever I get to
deliver a blow, you know, I'm I'm going
to take pride in that and I'mma, you
know, do the best of my ability to try
to knock your head off. you know, if I
get a, you know, a quarterback that is
trying to run, I'm going to make sure I
clear a path for him, you know, and put
my body on the line for that. So, um, I
love pass protection. You know, I love
trying to hit people. You know, I'm a
football player end of the day. I used
to play defense back in the day. So, um,
I got a little bit of craziness to me,
you know. So, pass protection is is key
for success.
>> Jeremiah Cameron, Cox, 12 News. Welcome
to the Valley. I think Paris Johnson Jr.
agrees with that statement. Uh what does
it mean to have some of your teammates
here to support you today? And then what
most excites you about joining the
Cardinals?
>> Just uh being able to build a
brotherhood. You know, obviously I got
Perez, I got Marv here. Um they took the
time out of their day to come and see me
and that means a lot. You know, that
shows that, you know, there's a
brotherhood at uh here at the Cardinals.
And I'm just happy to be, you know, uh
being able to be a part of that. you
know, I plan to come in and and build a
great relationship with these guys, get
to know them more um because, you know,
they just know me on a service level.
You know, I want to get to know them
more as people off the field and um
that's what I plan to do coming in. Um
but it means the world to me to see
these guys come in here and just, you
know, show their faces because at the
end of the day, they didn't have to do
that, but they did. So, that just shows
me the great culture that's here at the
Cardinals, and I plan to come in, you
know, make that culture better.
>> Jeremiah, Zack Gershman, a carinal.com.
Good to see you again. Uh yesterday you
were talking a ton about competing. What
is it specifically about competing that
you enjoy the most?
>> Just being able to compete against great
players, you know. Um I've always been a
competitor, you know, whether it's in
football, whether it's in ping pong.
See, they got a ping pong table in
there. So I'm going to get I'm going to
get with the guys on that. But I mean, I
just like competing, you know, um at
anything, you know. It could be
football, it can be in the classroom, it
can be in pingpong, it could be at
swimming or whatever it may be. I'm just
a competitor. Um, but as far as this
league, the NFL is built up of the best
players in the game. So, I'm excited to,
you know, team up with great players
like these guys over here and then also
play against some great players. You
know, I get to play against uh Jadarian
Jadarian Price, you know, this upcoming
season. He's a great player and I can't
wait to, you know, do a little jersey
swap with him, too. So, uh, I'm just
excited to compete with great players
and that's really what this is all
about.
>> Hey, Jeremiah, congratulations. Uh,
David Brandt from the Associated Press.
Um, you know, for whatever reason, the
past 20 or so years, not many running
backs have been drafted as high as you,
but when they have been, you know, it's
been guys like Saquon Barkley or Bejian
Robinson who have had big impacts. What
What do you think an elite running back
can bring to a team and and why is that
so important?
>> Just that, you know, that ability to
keep drives going. You know, you got to
be able to do good and short yardage.
You got to be able to score those tough
touchdowns. And you know, guys like
Seaquin, guys like Bon, guys like Ash
and Jensy, you know, all those guys can
do that. And um, you know, I'm no
different. I'm going to come into this
league and I'm going to put a lot of
emphasis on making sure that we can
extend drives, we can, you know, finish
when we get down in the red zone. Um,
and that's what makes a a running back
great. You know, a running back is
supposed to make the the the defense
rest longer and it's supposed to make uh
the offense, you know, score touchdowns.
you know, obviously, you know, block and
allow guys like Marv to, you know, run
those deep balls and allow a quarterback
to throw that deep ball and he can get
that and get a touchdown, but running
backs are very crucial for um a team
success and that's why it's, you know,
very important to have a good one. So, I
feel very honored to um be drafted as
high as I was. There's a lot of
responsibility that comes with that.
Like I think Spider-Man said, with great
power comes great responsibility. So, um
I am going to make sure that I uphold to
that legacy and uh of of having a good
running back and allowing them to have
uh a lot of team to have great success
and I'm going to come in and work to do
that. You know, I'm I'm ready to work.
Glad to be here and like I said, we're
going to do some great things in in
Arizona.
>> Jeremiah, you mentioned at the very
beginning kind of the the impact of your
family support system, your parents both
being police officers, being raised in
that environment. I guess kind of how
what impact has that had on you growing
up and and how has that translated to
the person that you are today?
>> Yes. So, my parents, you know, being
police officers, they were uh they're
army veterans as well. So, um you can
only imagine what that household was
like. It wasn't very, [laughter]
you know, you can only imagine, man. I
mean, that my dad, you know, wasn't very
strict, but he made sure I was doing the
right things at all times. You know, my
mom was the same way. Um, you know, they
were they enforced the law, so they
enforced rules in the house. You know, I
couldn't do certain things, but all
those things got me to being here today.
Um, you know, they instilled principles
of discipline in me. Um, my dad always
talks about consistently as a man, he
always talks about word is bond. So, um,
I mean, as a as a man today and as a as
a player today, I'm very disciplined.
You know, I got a D3 from my from my uh
running back coach, Coach Dean McCulla,
being detailed, dependable, and
disciplined. So, I try to live by those
principles, you know, every single day
and um they're always going to stick
with me for the rest of my life. But my
parents are the first ones that that
instilled those principles in me. And um
that's allowed me to be the player I am
today.
>> Jeremiah Bob McMahon of Arizona
Republic. Uh welcome. Back to Spider-Man
for a minute. Um [laughter] you were shy
and introverted as a young young man,
young a young kid. Where did how much
strength did you find from that
selfisolation and and your alter ego?
You you're already writing about it,
creating it. Uh and in the Jer Monster,
can you talk about that path in your
life?
>> Yeah, of course. So, um Jerem is a comic
that I released uh past this past
October and I literally did no work on
it. My dad right here did all the work.
Made sure I had a great team surrounding
me that made sure I was being portrayed
in a right. in the right way. So that's
Jerem. Um but I mean, you know, me being
an introvert, so you say. Um this just
allowed me to be me, you know, at all
times. You know, I'm I'm I'm a to myself
guy, um when I choose to be, but I can
also be a guy that that connects with
people. Um I got a, you know, on and off
switch. I can do both. But um me being,
you know, in the house and just being to
myself, you know, growing up has allowed
me to just be authentically me. And I
feel like um a lot of kids growing up
should, you know, invest in themselves
and get to know themselves because at
the end of the day, you are all you got
in this world. So um yeah, man, invest
in yourself and and and find out who you
are. And that's what I did at a young
age, which is allowed me to be myself.
And uh yeah.